<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Marcador Bozó</string>


    <!-- INTRUÇÕES -->
    <string name="comoJogar">How to play?</string>
    <string name="Texto1">First you will need a cup of Bozo and five dice.</string>
    <string name="Texto2">After the participants will have to decide who will start. To the many ways we more explanation. The player who is starting will put the 5 dice inside the cup and shake until blended and then throws on the table, there removes the glass being careful not to untap the data. If given after the cup is untapped are one on top of another error that move is not counted and the player can play again. Recalling that the time to mix the data in the cup\'s mouth it must be closed to not drop any data out. then made the first move the player will still have two more chances to throw the dice. So just to confirm after the first play he chose what kind of play will want.</string>
    <string name="Texto3">Types of moves the arrow to the right</string>
    <string name="Texto4">The types of possible moves within the Bozo are these: AZ, Duke, Suit, Court, Quina, Sena, Full, Then Square, General, as illustrated below. The but you can mark what you want, another good player follows a strategy.</string>
    <string name="Marcacao">Marking</string>
    <string name="Texto5">When the dice he will give you 5 valores.Usando the basic strategy you will choose the values that are repeated more or worth amis points. It\'s just you remember that to mark should add the values obtained by particular game you choose with Full exceptions, Then Square and General, why these plays already have a set score.</string>
    <string name="Texto6">Time to score points you can not add all the points but choose a type of game and then you can add. For example if I have two deuces and 3 corners in the first move of the three possible. But assuming I want to corner as worth more points and is the one that is repeated so we add all totaling 15 points and corner table in our app you will score in corner. I make you a note dukes 2 and 3 machines TBM is a full play and is still mouth. So I can score 15 points in the table on Full move. But if the move is General of mouth. Ai the value becomes 100 points and the move is completed immediately because the player who made the general\'s mouth wins the match with the independent sovereign point if another player is winning.</string>

    <string name="txtComojogarLer">Let\'s learn how to play Bozo First of all you will need. a cup of Bozo and Five data. After Participants will have to decide who will start Á several ways to desidir that more will the explanation. The player who is starting will put the five data in the cup and shake until blended. And then throws on the table. Ai remove the glass carefully. not to untap the data. If given after the glass is untapped. Are one on top of another. This move error is not counted and the player can play again. Remembering! It\'s time to mix the data in the cup the mouth of it must be closed to not drop any data out of the cup. then made the first move. The player will still have two more chances to throw the dice. Just to confirm. After the first move he will choose what kind of play will want to do. If you want more details of the moves push the screen to the left or click the right arrow to more informções. The types of possible moves within the Bozo. Are these. The. Duke. Suit. Block. Quina. Seine. FUL. Then. Square. General. As in the illustration below. The mark you make. It will depend on the stones that come, fter the three shots. But you can mark what you want. For a good player follows a strategy. Since we\'re talking strategy, using the basic strategy. You will choose the values ​​that are repeated more or worth more points. Remember that to mark should add the values ​​obtained by the game you have chosen. More has some exceptions like the move. FUL. Then. Square. General. Why these moves have already set scores. Time to score points you can not add all the points but choose a type of game and then you can add. I will give an example here for you. If I have two duques.E three cornered. In this example I will talk about two kinds of possible moves. Well first let\'s assume that I want the corner. Why it is worth more and is also the most repeated. Then I\'ll add these TES machines, totaling fifteen points. Then I mark on the table in our application. Fifteen points in corner. But the other kind of play. As you can see. When you have two data which is Duke\'s value. And TES data from the edge value. It is also formed FUL move. That perhaps it was made the first shot. And when such a move is carried out in one fell swoop. It uses the term play of mouth. then the play gets 5 points more and FUL. Becomes worth 15 points. Then I can score table. in Joagada FUL. An important example. It is the general\'s mouth. When the player makes a move the mouth of General ie if coming five stones of qualqer value all the same. General forty points. Becomes one hundred points. Oh no way. The player who made that kind of move. Win instantly with sovereign point. And the game is finished regardless of whether another player was already winning. Basically this is how you play a Bozo.</string>

    <!--Informaçoes de cada Dado-->
    <string name="TextoDadoAz">Or AZ play or also called the data number 1 Az is the sum of its values which can vary from 1 to 5 points.</string>
    <string name="lerAz">The data AZ or peace move. It can also be called the number one given AZ has the sum of its values that can range from one to five points.</string>

    <string name="TextoDadoDuque">Or Duke play or also called the data number 2 Duke is the sum of its values which can vary from 2 to 10 points.</string>
    <string name="lerDuque">Given Duke or Duke play can also be called the number two given Duke has the sum of its values can range from two to ten points.</string>

    <string name="TextoDadoTerno">Or play suit or also called the data number 3 has suit the sum of their values may vary from 3 to 15 points.</string>
    <string name="lerTerno">Dado suit or move Suit can also be called the number Three has given suit the sum of its values that can vary from three to fifteen points.</string>

    <string name="TextoDadoQuadra">Or block or move also called number 4 since the court is the sum of its values which may vary from 4 to 20 points.</string>
    <string name="lerQuadra">Given the court or move court. It may also be called the number four is given Court the sum of its values which may vary from four to twenty points.</string>

    <string name="TextoDadoQuina">Cinchona or play or also called the data number 5 has Cinchona the sum of its values which may vary from 5 to 25 points.</string>
    <string name="lerQuina">Dado Quina Quina or move. It can also be called Five number. The Quina has given the sum of its values can range from five to twenty-five points.</string>

    <string name="TextoDadoSena">Seine or move or also called the number 6 on the Sena has given the sum of its values that can vary from 6 to 30 points.</string>
    <string name="lerSena">Data Sena or Sena move can also be called the number given six Sena has the sum of its values can range from six to thirty points.</string>

    <string name="TextoDadosFull">In order to form the full play you need the five dice. Two data must be of a value since the other three data valor.Por another example the first two data values are 6-6 the other three data would be 4-4-4 and in encima illustration. The value of the play is full of 10 points but the move is of mouth value becomes 15 points.</string>

    <string name="lerFull">Ful order to form FUL play you need the five dice data must be of a value since the other three data other value for example. The first two data values are six Six and the other three data would Four Four Four as in the illustration on top. The value of Ful move is ten points but if the move is the value of mouth becomes fifteen points. More what is Ful mouth? Ful mouth is when the play is performed once.</string>

    <string name="TextoDadosSeguida">To form the next move. There are two types of sequence data. The first sequence is from 1 to 5 and the other sequence is from 2 to 6 e.g. 1-2-3-4-5 and 2-3-4-5-6 would be another sequence. As in encima illustration. The value to be marked then the play is 20 points but if the move is to mouth the point becomes 25.</string>

    <string name="lerSeguida">Then. To form the next move there two types of sequence data. The first sequence is from 1 to five, and the other sequence is from 2 to six. For example. One Two Three Four and Five and the other sequence would be. two three four five six. As in encima illustration. The value to be marked then the move is twenty points. But if the move is to mouth the point becomes vite-five. More which is followed by mouth? Then mouth is when the move is performed once.</string>

    <string name="TextoDadosQuadrada">To be able to play a square must have four equal numbers. For example 2-2-2-2 as in the illustration on top. These four equal data can be of any value and the value that should be marked in the square pass is 30 points. But if the square is the mouth of the value becomes 35 points.</string>

    <string name="lerQuadrada">Square to be able to make a square move must have four equal numbers For example Two Two Two and Two As in encima illustration these four data equal can be of any value and the value that should be marked on the play square is thirty points but if the square for the mouth of the value becomes thirty-five points. More what it is square of mouth? mouth is square when play is performed once.</string>

    <string name="TextoDadosGeneral">To form the General move you will need all five data are of the same value For example 5-5-5-5-5 data can be of any value if they are equal. The value to be marked on the move General is forty points. But if the move is General of mouth. Ai the value becomes 100 points and the move is completed immediately because the player who made the general\'s mouth wins the match with the sovereign point, regardless of whether another player is winning.</string>

    <string name="lerGeneral">General to form the general move you will need all five data are of the same value for example. Five, five, five, five, and five. Such data may be any value. Since they are equal. The value to be marked on the move General is forty points. But if the move is General of mouth. Ai the value becomes a hundred points. And the move is terminated immediately. Because the player who made the general\'s mouth. Wins the game with the sovereign point. Regardless if another player is winning. More what is general of mouth? General\'s mouth when the move is performed once. And will round ends.</string>
    <string name="XRiscar">X Scratch</string>
    <string name="adicionar">Add</string>
    <string name="adicionarJogador">Add player</string>
    <string name="apagar">Delete</string>
    <string name="apagarMarcador">Delete Bookmark</string>
    <string name="aviso">Notice</string>
    <string name="cancelar">Cancel</string>
    <string name="comecar">Begin</string>
    <string name="compartilharApp">Share APP</string>
    <string name="criarUmMarcador">Create a bookmark</string>
    <string name="dadosDoMarcador">Bookmark data</string>
    <string name="descartar">Discard</string>
    <string name="descartar_alteracoes">Discard Changes</string>
    <string name="empate">A tie</string>
    <string name="erroApagarMarcador">Error deleting bookmark</string>
    <string name="finalizar">Finish</string>
    <string name="finalizarRodada">Finish round</string>
    <string name="foiAdicionado">was added</string>
    <string name="ganhador">Winner</string>
    <string name="ganhadoresPorRodada">Winners per round</string>
    <string name="ganhando">Winning</string>
    <string name="inciarMarcador">Start Bookmark</string>
    <string name="jogador">Player</string>
    <string name="jogar">Play</string>
    <string name="limiteJogadores">Limit 10 players</string>
    <string name="marcador">Highlighter</string>
    <string name="marcadorApagado">Marker off</string>
    <string name="marcadorDoBozo">Bozó Scoreboard</string>
    <string name="marcadoresSalvos">Saved bookmarks</string>
    <string name="menssagem_salvar_grupo">You can save your bookmark if you want to play later.</string>
    <string name="nenhumMarcador">No Bookmarks</string>
    <string name="nenhum_jogador_adicionado">No player was added</string>
    <string name="nomeGanhador">Winning name</string>
    <string name="nomeJogador">Player name</string>
    <string name="nomeMarcador">Name Score</string>
    <string name="novoMarcador">New bookmark</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="ops">Oops!</string>
    <string name="parar">Stop</string>
    <string name="placar">Score</string>
    <string name="placarDaRodada">Round Score</string>
    <string name="pontos">Points</string>
    <string name="primeiro">First</string>
    <string name="proximo">Next</string>
    <string name="recurso_nao_suportado">Feature not supported on your device</string>
    <string name="remover">Remove</string>
    <string name="removerJogador">Remove player</string>
    <string name="requer_jogador">Almost there! Add only 1 player to start</string>
    <string name="requer_jogadores">Oops! Add at least 2 players to get started</string>
    <string name="rodada_incompleta">Some players have not yet completed all the spaces. Do you want to quit?</string>
    <string name="sair">Exit</string>
    <string name="sairDoMarcador">Exit bookmark</string>
    <string name="sair_sem_jogar">You did not play any round.\nDo you want to leave anyway?</string>
    <string name="salvando">Saving just a moment ...</string>
    <string name="salvar">Save</string>
    <string name="salvo_com_sucesso">saved successfully</string>
    <string name="tabela">Table</string>
    <string name="texto1Welcome3">Here you add marker name and players</string>
    <string name="texto2Welcome3">First</string>
    <string name="texto3Welcome3">Bookmark Name</string>
    <string name="texto4Welcome3">Lastly</string>
    <string name="texto5Welcome3">Name of players</string>
    <string name="textoAdicionarJogadores">Now add the players to start. Remember a maximum of 10 players.</string>
    <string name="textoApagarMarcador">Delete bookmark</string>
    <string name="textoCompartilharApp">Download Bullet Bozo on Google Play</string>
    <string name="textoLimeiteJogadores">Oops! You can only add up to 10 players</string>
    <string name="textoNovaPartida">First you need to write a name for your Bozo Scoreboard</string>
    <string name="textoOpsRemoverJogador">You can not remove more players. The marker must have at least 2 players.</string>
    <string name="textoOutraRodada">Want to play another round?</string>
    <string name="textoRemoverJogador">This player is no longer going to play.\nAre you sure?</string>
    <string name="textoWelcome1">You should have a glass of bozó with 5 dice</string>
    <string name="textoWelcome2">To create a new click on the Start button</string>
    <string name="textoWelcome3">In this screen you will mark the values that you can play with the bozó cup</string>
    <string name="texto_decisao_empate">Players must decide on the dice.\nSelect the player who won</string>
    <string name="tituloPonto">Title point</string>
    <string name="titulo_salvar_e_sair">Do you want to save before leaving?</string>
    <string name="total">All</string>
    <string name="ultimoMarcadorSalvo">Last Saved Score</string>
    <string name="valores">Values</string>
    <string name="voltar">Back</string>
    <string name="textoAdicionarNomeMarcador">You must add a name for your bookmark</string>
    <string name="textoRodada">Congratulations!\nBest player of this round</string>
    <string name="definicoes">Definitions</string>
    <string name="desligado">Off</string>
    <string name="ligado">On</string>
    <string name="luz_de_fundo_no_marcador">Backlight on marker</string>
    <string name="pecasTrocadas">"Parts exchanged for "</string>
    <string name="sobre">About</string>
    <string name="textoDesligado">Backlight Off</string>
    <string name="textoLigado">Backlight On</string>
    <string name="textoDialogValoresPecas">"Select the value of the part you want for your marker "</string>
    <string name="valoresTabela">Table Values</string>
    <string name="versao">"Version : "</string>
    <string name="versao_padrao">Version : 1.1</string>
    <string name="todos_direitos_reservados">All rights reserved.</string>
    <string name="instrucoes">Instructions</string>
    <string name="alterar">Change</string>
    <string name="alterar_copo_bozo">Change glass of Bozó</string>
    <string name="aplicar">Apply</string>
    <string name="atualizar">Update</string>
    <string name="comecar_tudo_de_novo">Start all over again</string>
    <string name="copo_virtual">Virtual cup</string>
    <string name="de">" in "</string>
    <string name="duque" translatable="false"></string>
    <string name="e">" and "</string>
    <string name="embaixo_selecionado">Under selected</string>
    <string name="espiar_valores_encima">Spying on top</string>
    <string name="full_boca">Full of first</string>
    <string name="general_boca">General of first</string>
    <string name="jogada">" played"</string>
    <string name="jogadas">" plays"</string>
    <string name="menssagem2">To play the dice turn the cup</string>
    <string name="menssagem_1">Click on the glass to be able to shake</string>
    <string name="menssagem_arrastar_dados">Drag the dice here to separate them from the glass.</string>
    <string name="menssagem_atualizar">You have not finished your move, do you want to update anyway?</string>
    <string name="menssagem_sair">You have not finished your move, do you want to leave anyway?</string>
    <string name="menssagem_visualizar">His glass of Bozzo would look like this. After that apply the theme.</string>
    <string name="nenhum_tem_restaurado">No topics selected</string>
    <string name="olhando_tema">Looking at current topic</string>
    <string name="para_jogar_dados">To play the dice turn the cup</string>
    <string name="pedir_embaixo">Ask for it underneath</string>
    <string name="quadrada_boca">"Quadrada de First "</string>
    <string name="restaurar">Restore</string>
    <string name="seguida_boca">Seguida de First</string>
    <string name="tema_do_copo">Cup Theme</string>
    <string name="tema_restaurado">Theme restored</string>
    <string name="temas">Themes</string>
    <string name="valores_embaixo_visivel">Values Below visible</string>
    <string name="valores_encima_visivel">Values on top visible</string>
    <string name="visualizar_tema_atual">View current topic</string>
    <string name="vizualizar">View</string>
    <string name="voce_tem">You have</string>


</resources>
